freedback.com 2004-06-06

# Privacy Statement for Freedback.com

**Privacy Statement for Freedback.com**

note.com LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all Webmasters.org sites run by note.com LLC, including this website: Freedback.com. 

**Policies for Webmasters (Website Owners) Using our services:**  
Our sites' registration forms requires Webmasters  to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zipcode, country or language). We use contact information from the registration form to send the Webmaster "Service Mailings", from us only, which include legal notices, new features and valuable tips, as well as promotions about our company and our partners. The Webmaster's contact information is also used to contact them when necessary. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the Webmaster's experience, and that of Web Visitors coming to our site through the Webmasters' site, showing the Webmaster and the Web Visitors content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Our site uses an order form for Webmasters to request our fee-based products and services. The payment acceptance system to which this form connects is entirely managed by iBill, a reseller of credit card and other payment services. We have no access to credit card information collected by iBill.  To view iBill's privacy policy, go to: [http://ibill.com/About/legal.cfm](http://ibill.com/About/legal.cfm). Contact information provided in ordering our fee-based services is used to configure forms, and to send information as well as promotions, through Service Mailings conducted by us only, about our company, and our partners to our member Webmasters. The Webmaster's contact information is also used to get in touch with the Webmaster when necessary. 

Webmasters who sign up for our Affiliate Program provide additional data about their legal entities to effectuate payment of revenue earned through the program. 

As noted above, our Service Mailings include periodic notices to our member Webmasters regarding new features, legal notices, and valuable tips. Because the Service Mailings are the only method of sending legal notices to member Webmasters, a Webmaster cannot unsubscribe from Service Mailings without terminating his/her use of our service. 

**Policies for Web Visitors (Surfers) Using our Service**  
most Web Visitors come to our site after they have filled out submission forms on the sites operated by member Webmasters participating in our service. We pass all data that a Web Visitor enters to the Webmaster of the site on which the submission form is located. At the same time, we bring the Web Visitor to our website where we can present them with advertising on our response page. If the advertising on our site contains a submission form we may autopopulate this form with data extracted from the previous form submission on the member Webmaster's site. We will not disclose ANY data on an individual Web Visitor to an advertiser unless the Web Visitor gives his/her permission to do so, usually by clicking on a button in the advertising form which submits the data to the advertiser. However, we may share Web Visitor data with our advertisers in the aggregate. 

**Policies for both Webmasters and Web Visitors**  
 _Links to other sites_ : The advertisements on our site may contain links to other sites. **Freedback.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Before submitting data to an advertiser site, it is the Web Visitor's responsibility to ascertain the advertiser's Privacy Policy and not submit the data if (s)he does not find it acceptable. 

_Cookies **:**_ Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to track users for the purposes of paying member sites registered with our Affiliate Program. Cookies are set from both this website as well as from the master domain, **Webmasters.org**. 

We use an outside ad company to display some of the ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Website, cookies received with the ads displayed through the outside ad company ads are collected by that ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

_Contests_ : We may run contests on our site in which we ask contest entrants for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zipcode, country or language). We use contact data from our contests to send entrants information and promotions, through mailings conducted by us only, about our company and our partners. The entrant's contact information is also used to contact the entrant when necessary. We may also use this data to tailor the entrant's experience at our sites, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Contest entrants may opt-out of receiving future mailings related to that contest; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

_Opt-in Mailing Lists_ : We have a relationship with PostMasterDirect as manager of our opt-in mailing lists assembled through forms on our site. PostMasterDirect uses a double opt-in procedure for verifying a Web Visitor or Webmaster's willingness to be on a mailing list, offers an opt-out procedure and does not share any personal information with direct marketers. To find out more about how PostMasterDirect handles the personal information collected for opt-in mailing lists go to [http://w3.netcreations.com/main?page=privacy](http://w3.netcreations.com/main?page=privacy). 

We also have contractual arrangements with affiliate marketing networks. Including Websponsors, Linkshare and Commission Junction. These affiliate marketing networks provide some of the advertisements shown on our sites. To find out more about how these networks handle the collection of personal information, please visit their provacy statements at: 

_IP Addresses:_ We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

_Choice/Opt-Out_ Contest entrants have the ability to opt-out of future mailings related to that contest. For each contest, the opt-out section will be clearly accessible by hyperlink, check box or other method.  Webmasters also have the ability to opt-out of our Service Mailings, provided however that if a Webmaster unsubscribes from the Service Mailings then he or she must also terminate use of our service. Lastly, members of our opt-in lists may unsubscribe at any time as described in PostMasterDirect's policies referenced above. 

**Security**  
We take the security of our data seriously and utilize several software and hardware devices to protect unauthorized access to our data. In addition, we monitor the use of our service to detect attempts at accessing our data. Any such attempts may be dealt with on a technical or legal level, as appropriate in a given case. 

**Supplementation of Information**  
This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For example, we may contract with a firm which identifies geographic locale of an IP address in order to better present the site (including our advertiser messages) in the appropriate language local to a Webmaster or Web Visitor. 

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [support@note.com](mailto:support@note.com)
  2. send mail to the following postal address: 

PO Box 234 Jenkintown PA 19046-0234 (USA)

**Delete/Deactivate**  
This site also gives users the following options for deactivating their account and deleting all information previously provided. 

  1. email [support@note.com](mailto:support@note.com)
  2. send mail to the following postal address: 

PO Box 234 Jenkintown PA 19046-0234 (USA)

As previously noted above, by deactivating his/her account a Website Owner will also terminate use of the service. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Alex Eldridge note.com LLC PO Box 234  Jenkintown, PA  19046-0234 (USA) [alex@note.com](mailto:alex@note.com)  

THIS STATEMENT WAS CREATED ON JANUARY 23, 2001. 

Privacy Policy | Terms of Service | Credits
